I was right that body that that
Americans always really fun I'm
Australian that's one of your first port
of calls you go you go shrimp on the
barbie you go throw another shrimp on
the barbie which is a weird thing
because that was that was an advert that
Paul Hogan did for Australian Tourism to
make you come out that was never aired
in Australia and you call them shrimp
but we call them prawns and he did it so
that you would feel at home in our
country and so the advert was Paul hang
on throw all throw another shrimp on the
barbie for you and then you're where
that must be what they all say all the
time what one Australian said it
once once it was said once by one
Australian and you think I'll just
bring that out all the time
what will you why are you out here just
on holiday or what which one this one
here I assumed it wasn't the Asian one
next year well I could have been adopted
or something but I did though I did the
ancestry.com did you know that woman or
you just were having a fight with your
sister and let the random you know who
that your wife or yeah yeah when you're
on holiday with your wife and your
sister it's just as the next person you
say I'm on holiday with my wife and my
sister yeah I go I'm on holiday with my
sister and whatever this thing is yeah
you don't do
you always always mention your wife
first and I can say that as a man who is
that about six women leaving so I've
learned some lessons along the way I
have I've lived with six women in my
life and they've all left and sooner or
later I'm gonna start blaming myself you
know what'll - I do yes how I said
Baltimore Seaway that's not far word
what made you come to LA just wanted to
wear a t-shirt I don't know a lot about
Baltimore I know the why was sit there
it seems like a hellhole I'm sure it's
very nice I'm gigging there in a couple
weeks I know that Michael Phelps lives
there and the wire that's pretty much
live right fragging - backwards from
there he was he was what if they went to
high school in Marin although you're not
the guy that looks like the authority
unto back
[Laughter]
I'm gonna have to take your word for
that one seems to correct yeah
oh are you want me to button up for this
bit all right I got I've gotten to that
stage in my life where someone dresses
me I had it at the beginning in my life
my mother used to dress me and now I get
dresses me and two comes up and goes she
comes up and goes like this straighten
your belt up oh oh okay it used to be
four years of my career as dressing
myself and then like I go to award shows
they like put a handkerchief in your
pocket and I pull it out and blow music
no no that's meant to harden no